JOSE ROBERTO V. RAMOS

Front-End Web Developer | Civil Engineer









engrjvramos@gmail.com 📞 0927-936-1818 🏟 engrjvramos.github.io 👩 github.com/engrjvramos

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Self-taught web developer and programmer with 4 years experience in construction and project management seeking a Web Developer role with your company where I can apply my technical knowledge and skills to provide users with sustainable, high-quality, and responsive websites.

EXPERIENCE

Pandora Technology Solutions Inc.

March 2022 - present | Web Developer | Makati City

- Developed 200+ template websites for 2 consecutive months using UCMS content management system and aaPanel as an open source control panel.
- Evaluated code to ensure it meets industry standards, is properly structured, and is responsive and compatible with browsers and devices.

Megawide Construction Corporation

September 2019 - June 2021 | QAQC Engineer | Metro Manila

Projects: Gentry Manor | Urban Deca Homes Manila

- Daily monitoring and inspection of work activities to ensure compliance with project specifications.
- Inspects and records all material testing & deliveries to ensure quality materials are used.
- Performs joint inspection with client site engineer.
- Worked closely with engineers in preparing, issuing, and recording of all QA/QC related documents.

PROJECTS

World Countries • Preview Live | View Code

An informational website integrated with the REST Countries V3 API to display common data of each countries.

Designo • Preview Live | View Code

This project includes 5 different templates that make up a 7-page agency website.

Space Tourism Website • Preview Live | View Code

A multi-page space tourism website built from scratch.

PayAPI • Preview Live | View Code

A 4-page marketing website built from scratch utilizing CSS Grid.

SKILLS

Front End

HTML5, CSS3, Sass, JavaScript, React (Beginner)

Back End

REST API

Tools & Platforms

Command Line, Figma, Git, Github, VS Code

EDUCATION

Technological Institute of the Philippines, Quezon City

June 2011 - October 2017

Bachelor of Science in Civil Engineering

REFERENCES

Romina Llena

Field Engineer Premium Megastructures Inc. 0917-304-5863

April Torres

HR Officer

Pandora Technology Solutions 0956-496-27509